(Happiness for Sale)
Nice to see you all.
It's been a while, Jae Hyeon.
- It's been so long. - You've gotten more muscular now.
I'm getting in more shape now.
- People say it's a new side of you. - Really?
Everyone has been talking about you.
- At Jang Woo's wedding, - Yes.
Everyone kept looking at Jae Hyeon.
- Right. He's so handsome. - Everyone took pictures of you.
- This is his prime. - I was so surprised.
I'm good at weddings, you know?
Exactly.
Just like your broad shoulders,
- you're brimming with confidence. - Of course.
- When it comes to weddings, - He got the poisonous needle later.
I'm the best man.
For today's clip, Kian84, CODE KUNST, and I worked together.
We finished...
a meaningful project.
The three of you got together while I was away in Kazakhstan.
We've been waiting for our chance.
Gosh, you're so annoying.
- What? - I'm done. I can't do this anymore.
- What? - I've been waiting for that day.
I wanted to join you for the flea market.
- The flea market? - You're sulking...
- just like Kkotbun. - I'm so sulking right now.
He has the same personality as Kkotbun.
You'll get over it quickly.
- Right away. - Right away.
How many years has it been?
- I might see ghosts here. - It's the break of dawn.
(Grand Opening, current time: 7am)
This is scary. I might see ghosts here.
I haven't been here in ages.
Where did you go?
(He carefully opens the door.)
(An unfamiliar place)
It's like I'm watching a movie.
Gosh, the last time I was here was three years ago.
- My gosh, seriously. - How mysterious.
This looks strange.
It looks like Hannibal Lecter might be in one of the cages.
No one's living here, right?
(He nervously walks in.)
- It looks like a horror movie. - Right.
- Or he's here to see a prisoner. - He's crying.
- He's crying. He saw someone. - What is it?
(Weeping)
- Gosh, the piano. - What?
What?
- A piano? - I had the piano.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
I didn't even lock this. Come on.
(He finally comes face to face with the mysterious space.)
The piano...
- It's your storage. - Yes.
You have a separate storage space?
- I do. - I see.
It was my first time visiting it after moving.
- You rarely use that. - I rarely go down there.
Well, I'm sure you know...
when I'm hooked on something, I buy first and regret later.
In the end, I'm helping our economy.
I help economy in many different fields.
When I went down to my storage today, I was shocked.
The music industry, restaurant industry,
and publishing industry.
I've been spending money in all of these industries.
The piano. Darn.
I didn't know I had the festive table.
(It's full of items he hasn't seen in a while.)
My gosh. This is completely new.
(He used the piano to practice for the fan-meet 7 or 8 years ago.)
My gosh. That was seven years ago.
- It looks like a good piano. - It's a great piano.
- Really? - Buying it was a big decision.
(But he's been neglecting it for years.)
Oh, the horse riding machine.
- An equestrian simulator? - An equestrian simulator.
I see. It's a workout machine.
That was my first house in Geumho-dong.
- That's... - I bought it after watching it...
on a home-shopping channel.
(He failed to get rid of it...)
(when he opened Moomoo Store last time.)
The machine was rotting in here.
I wonder if anyone's going to buy this.
To celebrate the new year, 2026,
I'm starting a grand project.
I'm going to hold the Grand Rainbow Bazaar.
As for the hosts of the Grand Rainbow Bazaar,
there's me.
CODE KUNST is my co-host...
whose wardrobe is ten times bigger than mine.
Kian84 is also my co-host who has a lot of random items.
The three of us will open the Grand Rainbow Bazaar.
(Trend Sensitive Man)
- Young 50s. - TSM.
(TSM spends 1,000 dollars on his hobby.)
- Do you still have that? - I do.
(All the latest trends belong to me.)
(He has all kinds of equipment, more than he can handle.)
(Hyun Moo, the General Store Owner as he has countless hobbies)
- You have so many hobbies. - Gosh.
(Fashion represents me.)
- He has so many clothes. - He must sell everything.
He doesn't wear them all.
(He has so many clothes that the rack is bending.)
Once you put it away, you never wear it again.
He has so much stuff.
(I'll store my precious shoes in my room.)
He has a lot of stuff too.
- He has a lot of stuff. - I do.
- Kian84 has a lot of stuff? - He has a lot of shoes.
I have a lot of shoes.
And random items.
(The experts from Moomoo Store...)
(and Seorae Outlet...)
(have joined the bazaar.)
(The grand hosts of the bazaar from different fields)
All of our proceeds from the bazaar will go to a good cause.
The three of us invited our friends...
who wanted to be part of...
helping out a good cause.
(The Grand Rainbow Bazaar lives up to its name...)
- I'm curious. - A lot of people came.
I see. So many people turned up.
(with its grand customers.)
I don't know where to start.
(Grabbing)
Oh, my!
What is it? Is it one of your early paintings?
(Oh, my. This is...)
I'm sorry, Kian84.
- Why? I see. It's Kian84's. - What?
- Is it Kian84's painting? - This is...
I've been looking for it.
I'm sorry, Kian84.
- Oh, that? It was a long time ago. - It was a long time ago, right?
- Wait. - Did he paint it?
- It was about 10 years ago. - It was 10 years ago.
(Kian84 gave a painting to Hyun Moo as a gift 10 years ago.)
It's fine as long as one of us can ward off bad luck.
I drew him a tiger for good luck.
- Things worked out thanks to that. - I found it.
Right. I put it back up.
(Thank you.)
This was when we first met. What a historical painting.
It's the one I took with my parents.
I should bring it to my parents' house.
What's this doing here?
Why did you put that in the storage? It's a family picture.
I'm showing how to be the worst son ever.
I see. That was the first step he took...
- as a bad son. - Think of it...
as my first step.
(The pile of dust marks the start of his journey as a bad son.)
(He takes out the inflator first.)
I have another one at home.
- Let's pull it out. - Why do you have that?
Why do you have that?
Why do I have so many inflators?
I had five.
(The next item is another inflator.)
(It's full of items he bought on a whim...)
(when he shouldn't have.)
Why do I have an inflatable tub?
You have an inflatable tub too?
This is part of my history too.
Okay.
(He goes back home with his long history.)
(Lugging)
He has so much stuff.
He recently bought the electric bicycle.
I customized it.
I pulled everything out the day before.
That's a lot of work too.
That's the most difficult part.
There's so much stuff.
(It will take forever to organize them.)
This is a great device. The ultrasonic eyeglass cleaner.
(He begins organizing them one at a time with determination.)
The sphincter strengthening device.
A sphincter strengthening device?
(He can't believe his ears.)
Let me see what's in my atelier.
(Is there anything else I can sell from this room?)
All the rooms except the living room...
- are used as storage. - Right.
I should pull out the oven.
Did I use this 2 or 3 times?
I used it when I made schweinshaxe.
A magic trick.
(When did I learn the magic trick?)
Let's sell it.
It's from Yamaha.
Wait. You have another one.
I forgot that I had one in there and bought it again.
- What? - So I have two pianos.
This was only used to trick Danny. That's it.
(The second piano was neglected after making him look good.)
I didn't use it at all after that episode.
What a waste.
The thigh strengthening device.
- How many times did you use it? - Three times?
(He finds the forgotten thigh strengthening device.)
- Everything is practically new. - They're all new.
- A final check. - Gosh, look at his clothes.
- You have so many clothes. - I tried to get rid of some.
But I still have a lot left.
(What's this?)
Oh, it's a ukulele.
This is...
I only played it twice.
It's brand-new.
I have 2 pianos and 1 ukulele.
I'm like a music major.
Oh, no.
(Struggling)
For fire gazing.
(Rattling)
I didn't touch it after the fire gazing episode.
The monitor?
(He made good use of it when he went camping alone.)
(A portable TV he used for fire gazing)
I didn't use it after that day.
Should I put this up?
Gosh, it's such a good device. Why didn't I use it?
- Oh, no. - I'm practically half crazy.
(He takes pictures of it to post it on the app.)
(Full of passion)
Let's put it up.
Gosh, I'm tired.
(As he had an early morning, his entire body is aching.)
(I should still try to sell it.)
Buying and selling items on this app is trending nowadays.
My gosh. This app has all the brands and items I love.
(He selects the photos he took with love.)
"Barely been used."
"Four hundred dollars."
Done.
(I hope I can sell it fast.)
It looks like I'm moving.
Okay.
(He's taking the items for the bazaar out of his house?)
All right. Let's go.
(Loading)
(He loads the car with the items 1 by 1.)
My goodness.
I have no more space left.
You can't fit everything in the car.
My gosh.
(Just like that, he leaves his house and heads somewhere else.)
Seriously. I really hope I can sell them.
My house is too small to hold the bazaar.
So I needed a bigger space.
I thought of a place that could give us the concept store vibe.
I had everything in my head.
(Kian84 and CODE KUNST are waiting for him at the place.)
- Let's hang all the jackets here. - Yes.
- I see. - That's Kian84's studio.
It's hard to find a big space like that.
My music studio is smaller than this.
It's a nice place.
The location is good too.
Where's Ae Ong? I don't see your cat.
I checked, and Ae Ong was in the usual spot.
(The two of them are displaying the clothes...)
(before Hyun Moo arrives.)
Gosh, you have a lot of clothes.
(Neatly hanging on the rack)
(Looking sharp)
(Meanwhile, Kian84...)
(is hanging the clothes without much care.)
(He finishes displaying them in an instant.)
- Are you done with your clothes? - Yes, I'm done.
(Observing)
- Kian84. When you hang them, - Yes?
They have to look nice.
- How do you do that? - Make sure they're hanging neatly.
If it's hanging like this,
- Okay. - they won't want to buy it.
- Really? I'm new to this. - Yes.
- Make sure it's aligned? - When you hang it neatly,
it looks stylish.
Right.
If it's asymmetrical, it looks like it's been stretched.
- Then it looks worn. - Right. It'd look worn.
You're right. Like this?
- Yes. That's great. - Like this?
A lot of people fall for this.
- It's really important. - Right.
(Neatly folding the pants)
CODE KUNST looks professional today.
The hangers should face the same side.
Clothes look great...
- when they're hung neatly. - Right. I should've been there.
I should redo mine.
(I want them to look nice too.)
No. That's not necessary.
I did an awful job.
If there are too many clothes on the rack, people miss a few.
I must make sure there's still some space left.
- Like this. It should be... - Didn't you work...
at a clothing shop?
Yes. I worked at many clothing shops.
Oh, right. I remember hearing you say...
you worked at clothing shops.
People will overlook some items if the rack is overfilled.
(Skillful)
It was around the time I was turning 24.
Back then, I used to work at a clothing store during the day.
I worked at department stores and vintage stores.
I worked there for a long time.
It's really important...
to hang the clothes properly, so they don't look stretched out.
The moment they don't look symmetrical on hangers,
clothes look stretched and worn.
I tried to hang them while making sure they looked balanced.
When I was a high school senior,
there was a certificate called Fashion Shop Master.
I studied hard for the certificate.
Try not to buy clothes displayed on the mannequins.
The clothes on the mannequins?
Here's why. On mannequins,
- their belly button is here. - That's true.
If you look closely, the mannequins are always standing on their toes.
- Right. Pins are on their feet. - That's right.
- They're standing on their toes. - They're wearing high heels.
- Let's say you buy the same outfit. - Okay.
- "How come it looks different?" - Right.
- Hanging them neatly is crucial. - Right.
You did this before. Do you have any useful tips on selling clothes?
You can't lie to the customers.
Let's say everyone can tell the clothes don't look good on them.
- "Gosh, it looks great on you." - Right.
- Right. - If you try to lie...
When salespeople tell you they aren't for you,
they instantly earn your trust.
- Right. - They actually sound trustworthy.
You have to work with the customers.
For example, let's say they try on some clothes.
Instead of saying, "That's not for you," you say,
- "This looks better on you." - Right.
- Then... - I see.
If we crowd the rack more than this, we can't sell anything.
This is perfect.
If the rack is too crowded, nothing really stands out.
Here's a tip.
- To make them look fancy, - Okay.
I have to misalign the racks.
- I see. Like in a zigzag line? - Length should look different.
That makes them look fancy.
That way, they can see the clothes in the back when entering.
For the three-dimensional feel?
- You're right. It's much better. - Yes.
It looks like we have more clothes.
- You're right. - You had a strategy.
- Of course. - You made good use of the space.
My gosh, CODE KUNST. You're different.
- Your clothes are more expensive. - Yes.
- My clothes are cheap. - Yes.
When they're thinking about buying your clothes,
we can give away my clothes as freebies.
The best piece of clothing I have is from Levi's.
Let's run that scenario. "Gosh, this is so cute."
"If you buy that, you get this for free."
"They come as a set."
- Yes. Right? - It looks like a better deal then.
"Wear this when you go out. And wear this when you come home."
- That's right. - That's a great strategy.
I should put some of your clothes on my rack.
Your clothes make my clothes look fancy.
That's a great strategy.
You guys mixed up the clothes.
- Right? - We did.
That's why I was so confused.
- Think about it. - That was our strategy.
- But... - I was worried that...
if we separated our clothes, they'd only buy his.
I thought, "These clothes look great."
Then I went, "My gosh. What's this?" I was shocked.
Come on. My clothes didn't look that bad.
Actually, Kian84 had several pieces of clothing that looked great.
- He did. - Yes.
I only brought good clothes.
- Of course. - Yes.
(Placing good clothes on the rack)
(Removing dust with a lint roller like a talented salesman)
- Just as I expected. - I can see he's experienced.
Right.
(Setting up the clothes smoothly)
Some of them were unopened?
Gosh. Just how many clothes do you have at home?
(Working hard)
I also brought comic books.
- Gosh, you have big feet. - Yes.
(Displaying an expensive item on an elevated platform)
- A laptop too? - A laptop? My gosh.
(Checking)
- Could you help me here, Sung Woo? - Okay.
The TV? One, two, three.
(I should sell the TV too.)
Wait. Did you decide to sell it on the spot?
All right.
I kept thinking until we finished.
"What else could I sell?"
- Let's put it there for now. - It looks great.
Concept stores these days have a comfy vibe like that.
- Right. - We're done.
You did a great job organizing them.
- Don't they look neat? - Right.
My gosh. Hey, this looks pretty legit.
You guys have a lot of great items.
(It turns into a concept store in no time.)
They all look brand new.
You guys have an amazing taste.
He and I have known each other for a long time now.
- Our teamwork was amazing. - Right.
But the thing is, CODE KUNST told me...
how we were going to arrange and place everything.
He easily convinced me.
Now that you guys finished setting up,
it looks like a real concept store.
- Right. - It's got everything.
Do you want to go and buy some food?
Let's buy some coffee too.
Let's grab a cup of coffee.
- Let's go down and buy coffee. - Yes.
We did a great job and were fast too.
- It looks great. - Yes.
We need to think more carefully when we buy new things.
No. I'm sure we had a good reason when we bought them.
- We did, right? - Yes.
- That's right. - Everything had a reason.
- It felt great when I bought them. - Of course.
- What? - He's here.
Hyun Moo must be here.
Like this?
- You're here. - My gosh.
We were leaving to buy some gimbap.
Do you want to come with us to buy gimbap and coffee?
I ought to.
(He says yes without a moment of hesitation.)
I was hungry that morning.
You didn't think about it even for a second.
- They were getting food. - As soon as you got there...
- What's that? - I have so much stuff.
- I'm going to sell everything. - Come in.
Is that a pogo stick?
- No. - Is this everything?
No. I have...
- about 50 times as much. - Give it to me.
- Give that to me. - Let's move everything first then.
- Let's organize them with coffee. - Let's do that.
Could you help me? Should I unload them then?
- Food... Yes. - Yes.
We'll move them inside. You can just bring them...
- to the door. - Okay.
(The three of them will work together to organize the items.)
We can hang more clothes here.
Okay.
They'd rather want to buy my fishing rod than that.
(They'd rather want to buy my fishing rod than that.)
The air pump has never been used.
- I'd hate to buy that. - Seriously.
(No one's warming up to the idea of buying it.)
(His car is filled with strange items.)
(Chuckling)
- Who can pull this off? - What is it?
Come on.
What's that? Hold on.
The pair is from Gucci.
It's from a luxury brand.
- The pair is from Gucci. - Really?
I got a 70 percent discount on an overseas shopping site.
So I had to buy them.
The shoes...
- I thought they were interest-free. - I had to buy them.
- They're a beautiful pair, though. - They're a good pair.
- They're a beautiful pair. - Yes. I like them.
They're made of real leather and from Gucci.
The pair didn't meet the right owner.
I was once hooked on this overseas shopping site.
- These promotions pop up. - Okay.
- You know the brand, Balenciaga? - Yes.
- Their windbreaker... - Right.
- had a 90 percent discount. - The one in a neon color? Right?
- The green windbreaker. - Yes.
- The size was triple extra-large. - Okay.
But there was only one left. So I bought it.
Really?
I wore it like a dress.
It didn't fit me at all. The sleeves covered my hands.
(That's how Moomoo's oversized look was made.)
I bought the shoes when I bought the jacket.
A neon-colored windbreaker...
- and red shoes? - Yes.
Hyun Moo, you're going to get arrested.
(A wrong mix of items)
- I brought everything. - Seriously.
- Some random items. - You brought everything.
Miscellaneous items.
Our flea market was fun to browse thanks to your items.
Right. I brought various items.
(Heavy)
What's this? He brought a lie detector toy.
Why did you have that at your house?
(The room is filled with mysterious items.)
The room filled up fast.
- Kian84. - Yes.
What's your take on this?
He brought pre-made croissant dough.
- What do you think? - What?
- What? - What's that?
- You can bake croissants. - Why did he bring them?
He must've taken them out from the freezer.
- He was just cleaning his fridge. - That's...
- They were in the freezer. - I wasn't going to sell them.
I brought them for a reason.
- I see. - Really?
We didn't know his grand plan at that time.
- Right. - Really?
This looks pretty nice.
Did you already set everything up?
(The 2nd-floor concept store is neatly organized.)
I see a few items I want to buy.
I wanted to shop like crazy.
(That's typical Hyun Moo.)
- Hyun Moo. Customers are coming... - Yes.
- at 10am. - Already?
- We have an hour left. - We must organize them quickly.
- I'll set this place up. - Okay.
They're quite useful.
(He takes out a box from a corner.)
They can just grab whatever they need.
- Just the cords, not the devices? - Everyone needs cords.
Right.
I see. They're freebies?
- I see. - No.
We must charge them at least a dollar.
- For the cords? - For the cords.
I have so many of them.
- Right. - But doesn't everyone have...
cords they don't use at home?
I'm sure someone will need them.
Hello.
- You're here. - Already?
Who's here?
Yes. I'm in the parking lot.
- Okay. I'll come down now. - Okay.
- The truck is here. - You brought more stuff?
- Yes. - What?
I brought everything from my house.
What did he bring? Oh, my.
I wonder if we'll find the owner for the equestrian machine.
- Gosh. That's... - There must be a separate storage.
When I saw the truck, I didn't know what to do.
- What's this? - That's...
- What's that? - You can put trays in there.
Then you can put the oven on top.
You can bake bread with it.
- Why did he buy that? - Even...
- I thought it was for Pilates. - Same here.
It's custom-made.
Even cafes and bakeries don't have it. It's a high-end oven.
- But you had it at home? - To bake bread?
Pastry chefs were so envious. "How do you have this?"
(The oven and rack are sought after by pastry chefs.)
For the past ten years, I held flea markets...
from time to time. But I've never seen them before.
He brought a great variety of items.
(Thinking)
I respect him.
We'll all leave this world empty-handed.
So while he's alive, he wants to enjoy a lot of things.
That's my understanding of him.
In every interview, it sounds like...
- He treats you like you're dead. - you want me dead.
(The poor, materialistic soul is angry.)
My gosh. That's dangerous.
- No. - Gosh, what are you doing?
- This? - Gosh. He's so manly.
Kian84, are you going to be okay?
- What? It's not heavy. - Are you okay?
That's a heavy stone. But he's carrying that too.
It's a millstone.
- That's really heavy. - Yes.
Whenever I see things like that, I want to carry them.
He carried the rack with the millstone.
Let's put this on the first floor.
(Large items that are hard to see at flea markets)
I thought I was going to break my back while carrying his stuff.
The equestrian machine is really heavy too.
It gives a great workout. I'm serious.
- Hyun Moo. - Yes.
Organize your things. We'll go and buy some food.
- I want an inside-out gimbap. - What?
- You're an oldie. - Gosh, no.
- Are you still in the 90s? - Preferences don't change.
- I was in elementary school then. - The one with the vegetables.
- I don't like tuna gimbap. - We'll just get something for you.
No. I want the inside-out gimbap with vegetables.
(He goes up to the 2nd floor after sending them off.)
(Grabbing)
There's something fishy about Hyun Moo.
(He goes down to the 1st floor with the croissant dough, )
(looking somewhat suspicious.)
(Pouring out)
What is he doing?
Hyun Moo keeps creating more work.
He's suspicious.
(He puts them straight in the oven.)
(Is he running the oven?)
The scent marketing.
Why do you think bakeries open early in the morning?
They spread the smell of bread on the streets...
- and make people line up. - That's right.
When people smell bread,
they'll go, "What's this oven?"
- He's strategic. - The smell of butter, right?
- The smell of butter is the best. - That's right.
(His mouth is watering already.)
(Moomoo's savory strategy...)
(gets toasted in a golden color.)
Do you want to buy snacks?
Yes, we should buy some beverages and snacks.
- Luxurious-looking snacks. - Yes.
High-end snacks.
- Thank you. - Thank you. Have a nice day.
(For breakfast, they choose hearty gukbap instead of gimbap.)
(They go back to the studio...)
(with breakfast to go.)
He set something up.
What's this?
(Staring)
You guys look like the young owners who have just opened a cafe.
- The fearless ones. - Yes.
- All right. - Hyun Moo.
Hey.
We bought gukbap.
- Gukbap sounds good. - We bought bean sprout gukbap.
Good. We only have ten minutes left.
We can finish gukbap in five minutes.
Okay.
I love that dish.
I'll eat that at home.
(Since there isn't much time, he hurriedly takes a sip.)
It's tasty.
Hyun Moo, it won't be right...
to bring down the price too much.
That's right.
- The profits go to a good cause. - Exactly.
If the price is too low, the buyers will feel bad too.
But sell your clothes at a low price.
(CODE KUNST, sell your clothes at a low price.)
- You know, - His clothes are amazing.
There's a crazy look in his eyes.
But sell your clothes at a low price.
His eyes...
My eyes go crazy when I see CODE KUNST's clothes.
I still can't forget the craziness he has shown...
when he came upstairs at my place in Seorae Village.
It's a Gen Z brand.
(He bought all CODE KUNST's clothes in Seorae Village.)
(Not even CODE KUNST could stop Hyun Moo's craziness.)
The white top I got from him...
turned yellow because I wore it too much.
- I wear all of his clothes. - Hyun Moo wears them often.
I wear them often.
Seeing him wear them often makes me feel proud.
I wear them until they become tattered.
We need a client like you.
- Exactly. - That's right.
- Clients who want to spend money. - That's right.
I told my friend to bring 2,000 dollars in cash.
Your friend? Who?
He'll come later.
- Will he come later? - Yes.
(He adds rice to his soup.)
I can't believe CODE KUNST added rice to the soup.
We turned you into a proper person.
Now, I can't do anything without eating breakfast.
It's a nice change.
(Slurping)
Now...
Why are you eating like a lunatic?
(Feeding on bean sprouts)
- He's eating all the bean sprouts. - Now...
Why are you eating like a lunatic?
- He's eating all the bean sprouts. - Hey.
He's gnawing on them.
Are the bean sprouts coming out or going in?
- The bean sprouts... - You know,
- the bean sprouts look aggressive. - Yes.
No, Kian84 is eating them aggressively.
It's like a comic book from Ito Junji.
I was happy that there were a lot of bean sprouts.
(Grunting)
My goodness.
I feel much better now.
We don't have much time now.
(They hurriedly finish setting up the 1st floor.)
Attention, everyone.
(That came out of nowhere.)
- Did you draw again? - It isn't like that.
Every hip boutique has the name in writing.
Would you bring the easel?
The clients should become excited upon entering.
Do you need an easel this big?
(Grand Rainbow Bazaar will shine...)
(with Moosquiat's new work.)
Isn't it pretty?
It's cute.
- It's cute. - Isn't it cute?
It looks a bit treacherous.
I think I've seen it in a loan company commercial.
- Moomoo Market. - Okay.
Isn't it cute?
- It's so annoying... - It's nice.
That he wrote "Market" in cursive.
Isn't it very old-fashioned?
Still, the color combination is pretty.
He's good at painting.
They're so nice to Hyun Moo.
Hyun Moo is good at picking the right colors.
Seriously, it wouldn't have been pretty without the red writing.
That's right.
- It's cute. - If I can't sell anything,
I'll sell the painting at a cheap price.
- I want to buy it. - "Market" is in cursive.
- Really? Do you want to buy it? - Yes. I'm drawn to it.
- The painting? - Yes, I'm drawn to it.
- Really? - Really?
- It's for a good cause. - That's right.
- Give me 50 dollars then. - I'll buy it for 50 dollars.
- Is 50 dollars a good price? - Okay.
I'll take it for 100 dollars.
- I really want to buy it. - Hyun Moo.
You sold your painting.
- Seriously. It's the first time. - He said the red was a nice accent.
CODE KUNST is good at business.
I didn't like it at first, but the red writing...
- drew me in. - It's an accent.
- One hundred dollars. - Spend some more.
- After all... - I'll give you 300 dollars.
Just spend 500 dollars.
- After all, it's for a good cause. - It's for a good cause.
- It's for a good cause. - It's all for a good cause.
- It suits your place. - I'll put it on the rooftop.
- It'll be nice. - Okay. I'll give you 500 dollars.
- Five hundred dollars? Really? - Five hundred dollars.
- It's for a good cause. - That's right.
It's my first time buying a painting.
I can't believe I'm buying your painting for 500 dollars.
- You have an eye for the arts. - You know,
- the first transaction matters. - That's right.
It's for a good cause.
It'll be better if you put your autograph on it.
- The value will go up. - I'll do that.
I'll write a journal as well.
Don't ruin it further.
- "Don't ruin it further." - It's my painting.
I'm the artist.
(The items are in their place.)
(What is Moomoo doing by himself?)
Will you set up the snacks like this?
I don't have anywhere to put them.
(What's that?)
Hold on.
- My goodness. - It's hip.
Suddenly, the piano looks...
so secondhand.
Suddenly...
- Isn't it like modern art? - Seriously.
It's like that modern art with a banana on the wall.
It's the worst.
(The unexpected artwork gives them a dopamine rush.)
(Giggling)
(Feeling overjoyed, he sets up more snacks.)
People can eat them and put the wrappers back in place.
(This time, he used a gap.)
(What's that?)
(He puts more snacks on the piano stool.)
Why are you putting them there?
(Stomping his feet)
I had nowhere to put all those snacks.
(For the visitors of the Grand Rainbow Bazaar, )
(snacks have been set up everywhere.)
He put snacks there as well.
Is this a picture puzzle?
It's like a treasure hunt.
- It's like a treasure hunt. - I can't believe it.
It's the worst.
(Highly satisfied)
It's funny.
(They finish setting things up as they laugh.)
- This place is cool. - How hip.
It's like Seongsu-dong.
(Full of the three members' items)
(The Grand Rainbow Bazaar is ready to begin.)
(Visitors' book, Grand Rainbow Bazaar)
Let's refill them when they're gone.
Someone is here.
- The first guest. - It has begun.
Who is it?
(Running over)
- CODE KUNST. - Hey.
- Dex is here. - Dex.
- Hello. - The first guest.
(A former UDT member with the physique from training)
(The textbook example of an all-around entertainer)
(They came to know each other through a trip.)
(Kian84 and Dex are close friends.)
- Welcome. - The first guest.
My goodness.
I invited him.
He doesn't buy many items.
He isn't interested in clothes either.
- That's right. - That day, he came prepared...
with a lot of money.
He came with determination to use money for a good cause.
- You must be busy. Thanks. - Now,
- there are many surprising items. - Really?
I came as soon as it opened.
- Well done. - Write in the visitors' book.
Write what you want to say.
(Dex: I'll buy many items.)
Okay.
Are you looking for anything? What do you need?
I like electronics.
- This is an electronics store. - Really?
- This is an electronics store. - Is this Yongsan?
This is Yongsan. The upstairs is Hannam-dong.
- Okay. - Seongsu-dong.
You're baking bread.
We're selling an oven as well.
- The oven is on sale. - You're lying.
- It's on sale. - Is it on sale?
- It's an oven from my place. - The bread looks tasty.
It looks tasty.
- I used it only twice. - It's in great condition.
- It's totally new. - It's totally new.
It's totally new.
It's what they use at bakeries.
Seeing such items makes me go insane.
Do you bake?
I don't bake, but I want an oven for some reason.
It's the best.
(Do you want to taste one?)
The smell is insane.
- Isn't it burnt? - What?
(There is so much smoke.)
- It's a bit burnt. - Why did you buy it?
(Hyun Moo comes clean.)
It cooks food very fast.
It might be a different matter once you taste the bread.
- That's what I'm saying. - The power is good.
This is an expensive glove. It comes with the oven.
- This glove? - It's for grabbing hot things.
It's hard to find a glove like this one.
- It's impossible to find. - That's right.
Where will you get this?
- The sales have begun. - This glove?
It's hard to find a glove like this one.
(They begin sales with the perfect teamwork.)
Here. Try one each.
(Try a mini carp bread each.)
It looks tasty.
It's crispy outside and moist inside.
Isn't it very tasty?
This oven elevates the carp bread.
It's tasty.
- Isn't it very tasty? - It's...
It's crispy outside and moist inside.
- It was very tasty. - Yes.
You don't need to look for the carp bread stands.
- I love that it isn't too soft. - Of course.
- It's like a snack. - You're right.
If you cook carp bread in an air fryer or a microwave,
it just turns soft.
The three of you are good at sales.
- We have good teamwork. - You guys have good teamwork.
You should learn how to bake. You'll be very sexy when you bake.
You're so muscular.
- Go shirtless and take out bread. - Dex will be sexy when he bakes.
Go shirtless?
- Go shirtless and take out bread. - Who bakes shirtless?
- That day will be Christmas. - That's right.
An adult's sexiness.
(Let me think.)
- Think about it. - Okay.
I've just begun.
Which snacks do you want?
Is there welcome food as well?
- Hey. - He eats snacks.
He eats snacks.
I see that Dex is nice.
- This is... - Yes.
- This is... - Is this piano for sales?
- It's for sales. - Everything is for sales.
- It's mine. - Is it yours?
I pressed the keys twice.
It's new.
Is this CODE KUNST's?
- It's... - It's mine.
Really?
- I'm a musician. - Isn't it a surprise?
You can try it. There you go.
There you go.
Imagine Dex playing a piano with that body.
- It's game over. - It's game over.
- And... - It's game over.
- drink this if you get thirsty. - That's right.
- Does it come with the piano? - I'll give you three boxes.
Hold on. Are these freebies on the piano?
They come with the piano.
- They have a strategy. - They're freebies.
Are these all the items on the first floor?
- On this floor... - There's this item as well.
- Don't miss it. - What's this?
You exercise.
What's this? I wanted to try it.
- Whose is it? - It's mine.
(It's mine as well!)
It's an equestrian machine with history and traditions.
What's this?
- Do you want an intense routine? - I'm a cowboy, Hyun Moo.
There it goes.
- If you ride this for 30 minutes, - It's nice.
- you'll sweat from your muscles. - Really?
It has good energy.
- Hyun Moo has had it for years. - That's right.
- That's right. - In which year did it come out?
Who buys products for good energy?
It's over ten years old.
Is it over ten years old?
(Hyun Moo!)
That came out wrong. It isn't over ten years old.
- He said it himself. - Seriously.
(He fails to say something that'll help with sales.)
I'll definitely fail if I open a business.
- "I made a mistake." - He became startled for real.
It's over ten years old.
Is it over ten years old?
That came out wrong. It isn't over ten years old.
- I kind of want it. - It's pretty cheap.
- It's pretty cheap. - How much is it?
I bought it from a home shopping channel...
for 700 dollars.
Ten years ago, right?
It wasn't 10 years ago. It was 7 to 8 years ago.
Why did you suddenly reduce the years?
- Since I bought it for 700 dollars, - Okay.
How about 520 dollars?
Isn't that too expensive?
Okay.
- It's for a good cause. - That's right.
- Hey, it's too much. - I mean...
- It upset me... - It's for a good cause.
- that he had added 20 dollars. - Yes.
It wasn't even 500 dollars.
(They aren't clear with the prices yet.)
It's so funny to see you guys exchange looks.
- We didn't decide on the prices. - No.
We were confused since he was our first customer.
All four members became flustered.
How about 520 dollars?
Isn't that too expensive?
- No. - No.
Let's look around some more.
We'll give you a discount.
Think about it as you check out the items upstairs.
- That sounds good. - Think about it.
CODE KUNST is good at business.
- You need to be honest. - Of course.
It's different from the first floor.
That's it. All right.
He likes it.
(The items on the 2nd floor makes a customer exclaim.)
What's this? Could it be...
- What? - I actually used this laptop...
when I made the fifth album.
- Is it for sales? - Really?
It works well. Everything works well.
This makes it perfect.
It has CODE KUNST's style.
- It has CODE KUNST's style. - You can't buy style with money.
Also...
Hyun Moo is helping.
Do you see this sticker?
- Yes. - You can't buy it with money.
- What? - Why?
Is it limited edition?
It's from an expensive speaker brand that's used by producers.
- That's right. - You get this sticker...
by purchasing that speaker.
- It means you bought the speaker. - Even the speaker...
I use it in my studio.
Each speaker costs 30,000 dollars.
Dex, it's like getting 30,000 dollars for free.
- I'm getting convinced. - Isn't that right?
- Did you work at Dongdaemun? - You know...
(Did you work at Dongdaemun?)
- Seriously. - I'll buy it.
- Think about it. - What's the price?
- I think 800 dollars is enough. - About 800 dollars.
- About 800 to 900 dollars. - Okay.
- It's a steal. - About 800 dollars.
- And... - What's that?
- there's this. - What's that?
I want to buy it.
What?
- You're a seller. - Hyun Moo.
- He meant it. - His greed suddenly came out.
If you decide to watch TV after enjoying a fancam...
- Is that yours? - It's mine.
- Really? - It was popular back in the day.
That's right.
We live in a high-tech world.
A high-tech world?
- What's the price? - What was the original price?
I bought it for 1,500 dollars.
It's pretty old. It's five years old.
If it's five years old, isn't it more valuable?
After all, it's an old version.
- You can't get it now. - You can't get it now.
- It's the early version. - It's limited edition.
- You can't get it now. - Eight hundred dollars.
- Eight hundred dollars. - I think that's a good price.
- After all, there's no remote. - Isn't it a good price?
- It's a good price. - Eight hundred dollars.
- There's this as well. - What's that?
- This is... - Oh, that?
- It's... - It's...
- What's that? - The air of the Grand Award win.
The air?
I captured the air when I won the Grand Award at MBC.
(It contains the energy of the Grand Award win from 2022.)
(He gave the air to CODE KUNST as a present in Mongolia.)
- You haven't opened it once. - No.
It's the air from that moment.
But that's...
I collected it like this.
(I collected it like this with care.)
- The air? - Energy.
Energy.
It's so funny that you brought it.
- The three of them... - Hyun Moo,
- weren't you moved that I kept it? - That's right.
I was moved that you kept it for many years...
- after I kept it for many years. - Exactly.
And it was time for us to pass it down.
- Will you sell air? - Yes.
- I collected it like this. - Sung Hwan, we're selling history.
That's right.
It's a talisman.
Then how much is it?
I think it should be 20,220 dollars.
- That's the original price. - That's the original price.
- But I'll make it 220 dollars. - It's 220 dollars.
What's this?
It's a cat toy.
After receiving that gift,
everything went well like magic.
- Really? - That's right.
The album I released afterward...
- became successful. - He became successful.
- That's right. It has energy. - Really?
It's still rolling around...
- in my studio. - Really?
- So no one bought it. - You'll become successful.
- You'll become successful. - It's available.
I'll throw in 100 more dollars and give you 600 dollars.
- With the painting? - I'll give you 600 dollars.
It's for a good cause.
- It brings good energy. - It brings good energy.
Kian84, close it if it's open.
(Okay.)
What's this?
It's a cat toy.
(A cat toy)
- Isn't it cute? - It's cute.
- Can't I buy it? - You have a cat.
- Why would you buy it? - For interior design.
- Why would you buy it? - It looks fun.
- It's cute. - Here.
Gosh, it's yours.
- A pepper grinder. - A pepper grinder.
- It's from Dr. Pepper. - Give it to me.
You need to buy it.
I'll take it if you don't buy it.
- Seriously. - Suddenly, I have a competition.
I just brought it out.
Someone else came.
- Did someone else come? - Is someone at the door?
This bazaar is popular.
Let's have them compete against each other.
Hold on.
That way, we can jack up the price.
No, don't jack up the price.
Dex is crazy about competition.
- That's right. - He's competitive.
Dowoon.
Welcome.
(It's Dowoon.)
- Dowoon. - Welcome.
Dowoon.
(The drummer of DAY6...)
(and the man of the sea who's crazy about fishing)
Dowoon.
Dowoon, write in the visitors' book.
The visitors' book? Okay.
- Hello. - Dex is here.
- Nice to meet you. - It's good to have you here.
- Hello. - Dowoon, there's so much to buy.
Here.
How old is Dowoon? Weren't you born in 1995?
- That's right. We're the same age. - We're the same age.
Become best friends today.
That's right.
- That came out of nowhere. - I was in a hurry.
Do you want to start from the second floor with Dex?
- Let's start from the 2nd floor. - Let's start from the 2nd floor.
What do you like?
I hate that there's competition.
You know, there are ethics in the business industry.
I reserved a few items.
- He did call dibs. - I put many items in my basket,
- so please don't... - Is this for sales?
(Looking around)
Is this for sales?
- Yes. - You recognize a good item.
- Yes. - It's sold already.
Come on. It isn't sold.
I actually used it.
But I used it less than 20 times.
- CODE KUNST actually used it. - I used it until two weeks ago.
Dex is very nervous.
- Isn't it sold already? - It's sold.
- Really? - But we haven't sold it yet.
After all...
- But we haven't sold it yet. - CODE KUNST is good.
- A competition should be made. - Once that happens,
things are bought with the thought of not wanting to lose.
Right.
It's our goal...
to reach the highest amount.
- Right. - Since it's for a good cause.
- How much is it sold for? - I paid almost 3,000 dollars.
It's being sold for 800 dollars right now.
- It's being sold for 800 dollars? - Right.
(What do I do?)
That's great. I think you can take it.
(That's great. I think you can take it.)
- Can I take it? - Yes.
- Right. Dex must feel rushed. - But...
- I'm feeling rushed. - Right.
These are all CODE KUNST's clothes, right?
They're clothes from all three of us.
There had to be more clothes than just mine.
I only want to buy CODE KUNST's clothes.
- We can't tell you though. - Right?
It's a chance to test your fashion sense.
- Okay. - Right.
- What? - Where are the hangers?
This seems like CODE KUNST's.
- Why smell it? - It smells nice.
Check out the brand.
- It's amazing. - It's a trendy brand.
- The brand? - Yes.
I'm not aware of brands.
You're a brand yourself. Why look for brands?
- Gosh. - What's the point of that?
That was a great line.
- Whatever he wears is of his brand. - Right.
People like us try to cover ourselves with brands.
- Right. - Gosh, what's with these people?
His body is a luxury brand.
(What's with this place?)
Gosh, nice one!
But it worked on Dowoon instead at that moment.
- Right. - Right.
Take a good look.
- You'll never find these prices. - Since there's a competitor...
We feel a lot more relaxed with a competitor here.
I'm the one who feels rushed.
- He's talking a lot more now. - I feel rushed.
I always do a smell check.
Gosh.
- This one is great. - This is cute.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
This one is cute.
- Really? - Nice choice.
- Try it on. - Right.
(The owners are delighted by the customer's great response.)
- Kian84 looks excited. - Can I try it on?
- We need a mirror. - We don't have a mirror.
- I'll use this as a mirror. - There should be a mirror.
A mirror? There's a mirror right there.
- Oh, it wasn't a mirror. - It's not a mirror.
Hold on. I think it will fit me.
(He uses his phone to be a mirror.)
- Try it on. - Whose is this?
- Don't ask about that. - Don't ask about that.
We can't tell you the owners of the clothes.
It's hilarious how he's holding his phone like that.
See if it suits you.
We didn't have a mirror.
It feels nice.
Gosh, he looks so cute.
It's the boyfriend look.
- It looks nice. - Dowoon looks nice in it.
- It suits you. Will you buy it? - I want to buy it.
- Really? - Yes.
How much was that originally?
- It looks nice. - This is Kian84's style.
That was brand new. It was really expensive.
- It was new. - It looks nice.
Right.
How much is this, CODE KUNST?
Let's check the price.
As for now,
- Make it an auction? - add things to the basket.
- Check out when you leave. - Right.
Let's not check the prices for each item.
- Don't start going wild. - Right.
- Right. This one looks nice too. - Don't start going wild.
- Add things to the basket. - These look nice.
(He looks relaxed as Storekeeper KUNST.)
- The lint roller must be used. - Are there things in here as well?
- You all were serious about this. - Of course.
(Moving inside)
(He enters the room full of mysterious items.)
What's this?
- This is a glasses cleaner. - Right.
- These are different cords. - I see.
- Take whatever you need. - Right.
If you like going to Japan, this is all you need.
- Just plug this in. - These days,
there are ones that have plugs for all countries.
- Those are heavy. - But...
they're this small.
- This is light, though. - Right. This is all you need.
Feel free to look around.
- Call me if you have a question. - Dowoon wasn't materialistic.
- He wasn't materialistic. - Right.
(But non-materialistic Dowoon seems to be interested in the cords.)
- Do you not have cords? - Well...
- I actually needed them. - What are these?
- Gosh! - I'll take these.
- Look at him! - I needed them.
- You needed them, didn't you? - Yes.
We have everything you need here.
Gosh, there's a fishing rod as well?
There's a fishing rod as well.
- Gosh! - You love fishing, don't you?
He bit the bait. This is the time.
He bit the bait.
He became a fish that day.
This was brought from Daebu Island.
- Really? It looks nice. - Yes.
He can't take his eyes off of it.
That's a great item for those who need it.
The reel... It's a casting rod, right?
The hands of a professional.
(He sets everything up and starts selling the fishing rod.)
This will be included as well.
The string has to be replaced anyway.
People who love fishing would love that.
What do you have inside your nostrils, Kian84?
As I dealt with so many clothes,
my nose ran like crazy because of the dust.
There was a lot of dust from the clothes.
- There's a lot more than I thought. - There are three rods.
That one was mine.
- Really? - We seem to click.
Right. It looks really nice.
I never wore that.
- Really? - It would be great...
if Dowoon wears it.
Right. It will be going to the right owner.
It looks nice.
It looks nice because it looks nice on you.
A nonchalant compliment.
Kian84 is great at this as well.
Kian84 knows what to do.
There are a lot more things to buy than expected.
Don't think too hard about it and buy the things you need.
- Let's see. - They'll be needed somewhere.
Let's see.
Looking up the prices was a lot of work.
- That wasn't easy to do. - Right.
I kept looking up the prices of the clothes.
- You needed to look them up? - Right.
Let's check the prices.
- You just got the things you need. - Right.
I can see that Dowoon doesn't buy things he doesn't need.
Things that aren't used at home have to be thrown out.
Right.
That's why Dowoon doesn't have anything at home.
- He likes keeping things clean. - Right.
(Dowoon's house is simple with just the things needed.)
- I'm so jealous. - Just like that.
You're jealous?
I want my house to look like that as well.
That's really hard to do.
Doesn't this look really nice?
- It's nice. It suits you. - Kian84...
has some gems with him.
Dowoon is quite like me.
- Right. - It's 500 dollars.
- It costs around 500 dollars. - Right.
Just give me 300 dollars.
Let's just go with 500 dollars.
- Let's go with 500. - Go with 500? Is that okay?
- Of course. - It's for a good cause.
- It will be donated. - Right.
- As for the fishing rod, - Yes?
It'll be a freebie.
(It'll be a freebie for the kindhearted friend.)
- That's a great deal. - Right.
- Let's go with that then. - There you go.
What about the cords and such?
Why don't we go with ten dollars for everything?
- Why don't we make it 40 dollars? - Okay.
- Feel free to pay more. - Right.
- We'll set the price to ten. - Okay.
I should write it down and put it up somewhere.
Let's do this then. We'll have it wired to my account...
- and collected later. - Sure.
- The fishing rod is a freebie. - A freebie.
- Isn't it more expensive? - He paid a lot for the zip-up.
- Isn't that the most expensive? - Right.
The fishing rod wasn't that expensive.
- He'll be paying 540 dollars? - Yes.
He's buying a lot of things.
- Gosh. - He spent quite a lot.
- It's going to the right owner. - Right.
It would've been a big mess without CODE KUNST.
- Right. - Gosh.
That was my mistake. I shouldn't have started that.
Not everyone can handle that.
- It's 540 dollars. - Right.
I have it written down. We can check later.
- Sure. - Right.
- The cords got sold. - Right.
Earlier, I wondered who would buy them.
I have five boxes of those at home.
- I'll get going now. - Right. Thanks, Dowoon.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Bye. - Bye!
- Thanks for coming. - Bye.
- He got the fishing rod. - I won't be seeing you out.
- Bye. - It got sold right away.
(Dowoon donates 540 dollars as the 1st customer.)
This one suits my outfit.
Why hasn't he left yet?
Dex has gone wild.
Gosh, he knows what's good.
Gosh.
- Gosh, this one looks nice. - That's perfect for you.
You have to sort of whisper it into their ear.
(Storekeeper KUNST's tip)
"He knows what's good."
- Without making it obvious? - The customers hear everything.
"He's different indeed. He has great taste."
A lot of designer brands have these.
Right? You can tell right away.
This looks really nice with black slacks.
- It's from experience. - Gosh, he's even styling me.
- I'm serious. - He's even styling me.
Okay. I'll add this to the basket as well.
(The owners feel proud.)
He's buying a lot of things.
- At that point, - That must be over 2,000 dollars.
He was shopping for over an hour and a half.
That is why people want to enter first...
when a flea market opens.
- You have to be there early. - Right.
- There's only one of each item. - Right.
This was designed by Drake, the rapper.
- Look at CODE KUNST go. - Hold on.
It's just for you.
- This is the perfect airport look. - That's insane.
Gosh, this is hilarious!
- What are these? - They're Gucci loafers.
They haven't been worn even once.
But it doesn't fit.
Make it fit.
- Squeeze it in? - Gosh!
He's a fashionista.
The Gucci loafers look this good on him?
- Oh, my. - Like this.
You have to walk around Hongdae in those.
Even though these are small,
you should wear them with the heels folded down.
- Gosh! - That's what makes you look cool.
Wearing Gucci loafers with the heels folded down.
How does that make sense?
What were you thinking inside at the moment?
"I'm such a bad guy."
(I'm such a bad Moomoo.)
They really didn't suit him.
(The loafers look nice, but they didn't suit Dex.)
Vintage clothing is worn these days.
They're worn like this on purpose.
- Jin Young looks great in these. - This is such a funny angle.
- The three swindlers. - That one looks expensive.
Someone else is here! Hold on!
- There's another guest. - Stay right here.
Hold on! Go around the first floor first.
Do you not have any work, Dex?
- Gosh! - Hello.
- It's Woo Il. - It's Woo Il.
- Welcome. - Hey, Hyun Moo!
I'm really curious about how Woo Il will react.
He's someone who brings home the leftovers.
He's a frugal guy,
- but he came for the good cause. - Right.
- He was determined to spend. - Gosh.
What? It's Woo Il?
- Woo Il is here. - Woo Il!
- Who is it? - Why isn't he leaving?
- Hey! - Hey!
- Woo Il is here! - Hey!
- Dex, nice! - Dex, nice!
- It's been a while. - Exactly.
Kian84 looks exhausted.
After his nose starts running...
I'm pretty much a patient at that point.
- Where must I go? - This is the electronics store.
- The electronics store? - The concept store is upstairs.
- The concept store? - Right.
Where should I start then?
- There's an oven here. - Right.
Are you interested in getting an oven?
No. I have no room for this.
- I don't really cook at home. - Here.
- I don't need it. - Hold on.
Oh, right.
(He quickly uses smell marketing for the dissatisfied customer.)
(His face brightens up thanks to the carp bread.)
(Dex heads to the 2nd floor during the welcome food session.)
(Rushing up)
(This is the perfect time to shop while everyone is downstairs!)
(He quickly goes through the items while everyone is away.)
Gosh, check out this jumpsuit.
There's an electronic device that's perfect for you.
What is it?
That's right.
He actually does horseback riding.
(The perfect item for Bacterrius who does horseback riding)
- But I barely used it. - Right.
(Why don't you give it a try?)
It's okay.
It's a better workout while raising the legs.
- Just think it was never there. - Leave it out.
- Leave it out. - Leave it out.
- It will work you out. - But if that happens,
it will make him think he has to buy it.
That came off...
even when I used it.
You can put it back on.
- But won't it fall off again? - Then you can put it back on again.
It can be put back on again?
That's how it is with life.
First of all, may I ask how much it is?
- Can I get a heads-up first? - Through a home shopping channel,
I bought it for 700 dollars.
How much are you willing to pay?
- No. I'm not going to buy it. - Well...
- I'm not going to buy it. - Even as an equestrian?
I currently live in an apartment.
Hyun Moo! This broke off.
It broke off?
- It was always... - No.
- The part is missing. - It won't get fixed on.
- It actually broke. - It actually broke.
- Gosh. - The horse got injured.
(In shock)
- Oh, no! - The horse got injured.
- But... - This really breaks my heart.
(But...)
Things will get solved if you buy it.
I have to be on it with one leg even if I buy it.
That's fine. It can't be helped.
- Gosh. - It's okay.
Let's go to Dex first as he seems to be done with his shopping.
- Let's check out his items. - Dex hasn't left yet?
Come with us. Go up and check out the clothes.
- There are clothes upstairs. - It's the concept store.
- This place is just a warm-up. - I see.
(They head to Dex after giving Woo Il some time to think.)
- Did you decide, Dex? - Yes.
Gosh, I love the clothes here.
(Impressed)
Why are you buying so many clothes? Gosh!
- These are all for you? - Of course.
The designer brands in between are mine.
- Right. - He got a lot of clothes.
Okay. Please check these items out.
You have to do well to get the prices.
Let's see. How much would this be?
(Storekeeper KUNST hurriedly looks up the prices.)
Should I ask AI?
We should ask AI right away for the items.
This is how we'll look it up.
- Will it tell you the price? - I bought it for around 800.
- It will tell me the price. - I got a discount from a friend.
We worked well together.
Kian84 was spot on.
It was such a great idea to ask AI.
It wasn't just the price of the item.
It was based on the current price or the price based on its condition.
It judges its exact value.
We live in a world with cutting-edge technology.
We wouldn't have been able to sell things without its help.
I'll take a picture of it.
Around 50 dollars?
How much is it?
- It tells you the price like that? - It's such a detailed answer.
This is 189 dollars.
- The original price... - It's around 180 dollars.
- is 189 dollars. - Right.
I think it can be 80 dollars.
- That's a reasonable price. - Right.
That's great.
- This must be a famous brand. - I see.
I bought that...
As for this one,
it's priced around 350 dollars to 450 dollars.
- They worked well together. - Right. We were the best team.
- That will be a freebie. - Let's give this away as well.
I think this will be...
- So he took the glasses cleaner. - Right.
We gave it away as a freebie.
That's quite expensive.
- Those are used in optical stores. - Right.
- I have that at home as well. - The cleaner?
- You do, right? - Really?
As I was buying that,
I wondered if anyone else would buy it.
- That's me. - Right.
You're buying a lot from us today.
(Woo Il starts looking through the clothes...)
(after big-spender Dex.)
Gosh, this is just for you.
- There are a lot of good items. - It looks stylish.
I'll get two caps.
- Give us 100 dollars for those. - It'll be 100 dollars? Okay.
How much was the equestrian machine?
I'll give it to you for 300 dollars.
- The equestrian machine? - We sold it.
- He has to use it with one leg. - Right.
He bought a lot.
- Someone's here! - Who is it?
Someone's here!
There are two guests.
(Two guests have visited.)
- Hey, Tae Gyu. Hi! - Bong Tae Gyu.
- You look so handsome! - He's so cute!
He looked just like his father.
- Gosh! - Gosh, you're so good-looking.
(Moomoo ran into him during his Fun Run.)
- That was hilarious. - That was so surprising.
(Actor Bong Tae Gyu)
(The actor who gets everyone's attention...)
(with his unique sense of fashion)
He's known for his sense of fashion.
- He dresses up so nicely. - Of course, he does.
You look like an idol star. Here.
Fill in the visitors' book. Dex is upstairs.
- I see. - Right.
- We write on this? - Right.
What do you want to write, Si Ha?
- What's your name? - Bong Si Ha.
- Si Ha? - Write your name...
and leave any comment you want.
- Bong Si Ha? - He's a great dad.
Right. He's impressive.
- He's adorable. - Hello!
- Hello! - Hello!
- It's Woo Il. - Hello.
Hello.
(Bowing)
- I belatedly send you my apology. - Why?
- Push it. - Why?
- For not noticing you! - It's okay.
I'm just Regular Citizen A.
(Actor Bong Tae Gyu, Regular Citizen A)
Do you know how surprised I got while watching the show?
What's your greatest interest?
This is the electronics store. The concept store is upstairs.
- Let's start with the first floor. - The electronics store?
Are you interested in baking?
- Right. - Are you interested in baking?
This is a machine used in stores.
- You're selling this? - Yes. This was in my house.
Try it, Si Ha.
- It's carp bread. - Thank you.
Give it a try and see how well it was baked.
- This was actually baked? - It was baked in the morning.
- Patissiers use this. - Why did you buy this?
- I tried to become one. - Right.
I gave up in the end.
It was so much work and I kept burning everything.
I had no talent.
I didn't want to make this go to waste.
- This can really be used. - Pattissiers use this.
Okay.
- Let's move on. - Okay.
Do you like music?
You like music, don't you, Si Ha?
- Do you like music? - He likes music.
(Ta-da!)
The volume can be adjusted at home.
There's no need to worry about making noise.
It has all sorts of functions.
Piano sounds to organ sounds.
- It can turn into an organ. - Give it a try, Si Ha.
- There are bass sounds as well. - Me?
- Give it a try. - Give it a try.
(Fiddling)
- How is it? - Do you take piano lessons?
No.
- You don't? - No.
- What do you play again? - The clarinet.
- The clarinet. - We don't have clarinets.
There isn't much to see on the first floor.
- Is that so? - Yes.
- Let's go up to see some clothes. - Okay.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
It's Bong Tae Gyu, everyone!
Gosh!
It's Bong Tae Gyu and Bong Si Ha!
This is my son.
- Hello. - Gosh.
- He's a comedian. - Hi.
- He's an actor. - Hello.
- Dex. - Dex is still there.
- When is he going to leave? - Dex is still there with them.
You know Kian84, right?
- He's CODE KUNST. He's a musician. - Right.
This is Bong Si Ha.
How old are you right now?
I'm 11.
- You're 11? - Right.
- I see. - You look handsome.
Gosh.
You came prepared, Si Ha.
- With what? - With what?
- Right. - Si Ha brought something?
What is it?
- I brought some paper. - What is it?
- He wants autographs. - Gosh!
- Don't mention it! - Autographs.
- "Don't mention it?" - Don't mention it?"
"Don't mention it." Gosh.
It's been a while since I heard that.
"Don't mention it."
"Inside-out gimbap." "High-tech world."
Is this a show from the past?
"Don't mention it."
Feel free to take a look.
(Let's start shopping while they sign autographs.)
Hey, Si Ha.
We can buy it if you find something you like.
- Okay. - Right.
Feel free to choose a hat or anything else.
(Looking around)
This would be nice, Si Ha.
- We're going to write certificates. - Games.
Right.
What kind of games?
- Board games. - Board games.
Do you not play board games?
Doesn't he play board games?
- He likes board games. - He does?
There are board games here.
- These are nice. - Why has he become a seller?
There's no need to go to a room escape place.
- You can play at home. - Right.
- This one? - Yes.
Is this one okay? He wants this.
Si Ha wants this one.
- I showed it to him. - Right.
- I showed it to him. - That was the best thing you did...
- this year. - I showed it to him.
He seemed really interested.
How much is this, CODE KUNST?
Around ten dollars?
Si Ha will buy it with his own money.
His own money?
- He brought his wallet. - Gosh!
- It's too expensive for him. - No.
- I have a lot. - That's too expensive.
- It's fine. - I have a lot.
I brought 150 dollars.
- You brought 150 dollars? - Yes.
- He brought 150 dollars? - You have a lot.
- He brought 150 dollars? - Then...
- He brought 150 dollars? - it'll be 60 dollars.
No!
- Why bring it up by 6? - Then 50 dollars.
What are you talking about?
Spending ten dollars is a lot...
- for an 11-year-old. - Gosh.
- Thank you. - They're done with the autographs.
- Thank you. - Okay.
I'll take a look at the clothes, Si Ha.
(Si Ha is done with his shopping.)
Let's see.
It's hard to sell things to fashion people.
- Right. - They have everything.
- They have a distinct style. - Come here, Si Ha.
This one. You should get this one.
- This one? - Yes.
I think it will look good on you.
Really?
- Should I get this? - Yes.
- This one? - Yes.
Okay. I'll get this.
(What's in this room?)
He has things like this.
- Do you sell this too? - This is really cute.
What is this?
- What's that? Bo? - Isn't that Bo?
If you look here... You can put a tissue in here.
Then you pull it out.
- A tissue roll? - Like how his nose runs.
- I want that. - It's cute.
You can hang it too.
- You can hang it or put it down? - You can put it down like this.
Since you got one, shall we get one for Bon Bi?
Bon Bi will find it cute.
- I think she'll like it. - Will she?
- All right. A gift for Bon Bi. - He got it for his sister.
How much is it?
Since it's for Bon Bi, I'll give it to you at 50 dollars.
- Is that so? - It's for Bon Bi.
It's for a good cause.
Twenty dollars.
- Twenty dollars? - Twenty dollars.
- Twenty dollars. - Twenty dollars.
- Twenty dollars. - Yes.
Do you need anything else, Si Ha?
Tae Gyu, don't you need Gucci shoes?
Dad got something like this...
- and threw it away. - Is that so?
You bought this?
It was an overseas direct purchase.
- Why did you get this? - Because it's from Gucci.
- Was it on sale too? - Yes.
But isn't the color pretty?
- If you pair it well with a suit... - That's right.
- They're pretty shoes. - Right.
The shoes are pretty.
- We are the problem. - That's right.
(The shoes aren't wrong.)
Doesn't Bon Bi need...
- a lie detector? - No.
Is that so?
You don't like any of the shoes, right?
Or a cap?
Don't you need to pump up a bike tire?
(Being clingy one more time)
We do need it.
I'll give it to you cheap. It's ten dollars.
- Okay. - Goodness.
- I need it. Okay. - I just threw it at him.
Good.
- Someone's here again. - People keep coming.
- Hello. - Hello.
- It's been long. - It's been long.
- Have you been well? - Yes.
(Hue Park is here after a long time.)
(The first Korean to win a Tony Award...)
(for his musical, "Maybe Happy Ending")
(A man with refined aesthetic sensibility, trained in fine arts)
- Have you been well? - Yes.
Oh, right.
- Please write something here. - Oh, it's like a guestbook.
- Then come up. - Okay.
(Let me see.)
It's getting filled.
Hue is here.
- Hue! - Hello.
- Hello. - It's Writer Hue Park.
- Hello. - Hello.
- He's the writer... - Hello.
- of "Maybe Happy Ending." - Hello.
Tae Gyu, the writer...
- of "Maybe Happy Ending." - Oh, I know him.
I don't have much things at home in Seoul,
so I'll do my best to shop.
You'd better hurry. They're going to take it all.
- We need to settle the bills now. - I'm shopping at heart.
- All right. Look around freely. - Yes.
- I'll explain them later. - Okay.
- Let's start with Dex. - It's 3,760 dollars in total.
Since it's for a good cause, I'll pay 4,000 dollars.
- Yes. - Goodness.
- I'll pay 4,000 dollars. - Okay.
(Dex's list of purchases: 11 pieces of clothing, 10 hats, TV, laptop, )
(eyeglass cleaner, complimentary, sunglasses, shoes, burger dish)
- He got a lot of things too. - He...
I think he got all of them...
- at a cheap price. - It was a good deal.
He even got a TV.
- The TV and laptop alone... - Of course.
They must've cost 5,000 dollars...
- at the list price. - Of course.
He got them really cheap.
- As for Woo Il... - His bill comes to 860 dollars.
- Gosh, Woo Il got a lot. - It's 860 dollars. Okay.
- Gosh, what is this? - Look at this.
I withdrew 1,000 dollars. It's 860 dollars?
Then I'll donate the remaining 140 dollars.
- I'll pay 1,000 dollars in total. - You'll pay 1,000 dollars?
Woo Il spends big when he needs to.
He withdrew that much with the intention to donate.
Woo Il is so cool.
(Woo Il's list of purchases: Equestrian machine, )
(shoes, hat, sweater, jacket, bedding sanitizer, badminton racket)
- It's 70 dollars. - He says it's 70 dollars.
- Since it's for a good cause, - Yes.
I'll donate 1,000 dollars too.
- No. - No.
- You can never. - No, you can't.
- Then we have to give you these. - No.
We have to give you a few more things.
- No, just give us three hundred. - Three hundred?
- We can't accept too much. - You shouldn't.
(Bong father and son's list of purchases: Board game, )
(a hoodie, a cartoon character tissue holder, sunglasses, )
(bicycle pump)
I'll get going now.
- That's incredible. - I'm leaving.
- You won't resell those, will you? - He got a lot of stuff.
- Thanks for coming. - Good luck.
- See you. - Good luck until the end.
- He swept it all. - I'm going.
- Bye. - Thanks for coming.
- Not at all. - Great work.
- Say bye, Si Ha. - Bye.
I'll say hi when I go running again.
- Bye. - Thank you.
- I'll get going. - All right.
I'll get going. Goodness.
What about the equestrian machine?
- As for that... - We'll send it to you.
- He said he'd send them. - We need to send the TV too.
- And the laptop too. - Okay. We'll send it to you.
- All right. - Bye. Get home safely.
- Bye. - It's raining.
Tae Gyu's bill is settled as well.
It's so tiring.
Oh, my.
There's a fitting room here, right?
- Over there. - When did he pick so many?
I suddenly got a dopamine rush.
Goodness. That's great.
(While the Bong father and son were being solicited...)
(Impressed)
Look at him.
I'll get going.
He got a lot of stuff while we weren't looking.
(He picked them out in earnest.)
(In no time, he got a big pile.)
Here.
- I suddenly got a dopamine rush. - Goodness. That's great.
I don't have many clothes in Seoul yet.
- All right. Buy them all. - I'll become a big spender.
I'll become a big spender.
He knows his stuff, seeing the things he picked.
All right. I'll try them on.
(Maybe a big spender)
(He tries them on in earnest.)
Over there.
(There's a mirror there in the bathroom.)
I love it.
- Right? - Yes.
Hue, that's yours.
- You didn't even look. - No, I didn't.
It's getting cold, so it's nice.
- This one is rare. - All right.
Gosh, this...
(This looks good too.)
Guess whose jacket that is.
It's a little confusing.
- Guess whose jacket that is. - I'd say it's CODE KUNST's.
That's right. It's mine.
(I knew it.)
What was that?
I was just happy that I guessed correctly.
He was really happy that it was CODE KUNST's.
- It looks good on him. - He wears it well.
- It's nicely oversized. - That's right.
- As for this... - Yes.
The embroidery...
It won't be pretty...
- if it's too tight. - Right?
- It's pretty. - It's pretty.
- Does it look okay? - Yes.
- It looks good on you. - The tag is still on.
(Gesturing without saying a word)
It's too much for me to pull it off.
I can't handle clothes with too much detail.
- You can't? - No.
- He has a clear preference. - He does.
It's genderless, so it'll look good on you.
(Soliciting without giving in)
- I'll just try it on. - Of course.
If you try it on, you must get it.
You must get it if you try it on?
I have a high expectation...
that my luxury clothes would look good on him.
He looks good in any clothes because he lives abroad.
I think it'll look good on him.
I really thought that would look good on him.
- I don't think this suits me. - It looks good, right?
- I don't think I can pull it off. - It looks good on him.
- It looks good on him. - It does.
You look like a little prince.
It looks pretty on you.
His image changed all of a sudden.
What do you think?
My shoulders aren't broad.
People like that should wear it.
People who are small should wear it.
- If muscular people wear it... - Goodness.
It's not a daily sweater.
On a special day,
when you want to feel good,
or when you want to party, it'd be nice to wear it.
Then they'll be like, "What's the occasion, Hue?"
"Your style looks great." Something like this.
- Is that so? - It's for an event.
He's so eloquent.
One thing for sure is that there is barely anyone who can pull it off.
It looks good on you.
- It suits him. - It feels like Christmas.
Doesn't it look best on him out of us four?
- It feels like Christmas. - I think you're right.
You're showing your style.
(You still won't get it?)
- I'll check it out in the mirror. - Of course.
It'll look like you're in New York.
- It's not as strange as I thought. - I told you so.
Of course not.
"I told you so."
- Okay. I'll consider getting it. - Sure.
- I'll try on a few more things. - You have many parties in New York.
Yes.
He's so smooth.
(Amazed)
- It looks good on you. - It's pretty.
- Everything looks good on him. - It looks good on him.
This one's pretty.
I even wore it once at the studio.
(He proved it's his favorite sweater.)
Great.
- I think I've chosen a lot. - I want to bring the clothes...
from home and refill.
Everything he tries on looks good on him.
He has a good fit.
Isn't this a limited edition?
It's new. It's totally new.
I've never played it.
Because I got annoyed.
I don't have a keyboard at home in Seoul.
I don't have a keyboard.
We have a keyboard.
(You don't have...)
(a keyboard?)
I was really surprised.
- You got him. - Both of them were surprised.
A songwriter wanted it.
They exchanged glances.
Follow me.
I turned on the keyboard and played it earlier.
- It's in great condition. - Is that so?
That's because it's new.
The pedals are still in covers.
I remember how older guys took me somewhere...
- at the Yongsan Electronics Mall. - No.
Or Dongdaemun.
- He's exactly right. - We don't touch their bodies.
Of course not.
Come here.
(Rushing in case he changes his mind)
(Amazed)
A keyboard?
(Entering the electronics mall on the 1st floor)
- Here. It's new. - It looks...
Oh, gosh.
You have good service here.
- It's welcome food. - Okay.
It's carp bread.
This is... Look.
I'll tell you the history.
I thought of myself as Moozart.
I wanted to learn to play the piano.
With that thought, I bought that.
(he bought his first piano.)
- It's Yamaha. It's the same brand. - Okay.
After I bought that, I got lazy and didn't play.
I shoved it in the storage.
Then time passed by.
I forgot that I bought it.
Then I decided to become Moozart and bought another one.
(He bought the second piano, dreaming of becoming Moozart.)
In conclusion, both are new.
- Both are new. - What's even funnier...
is that he got a lower-level one.
He downgraded it?
- This is better. - This is better, and that's...
Because I didn't know.
Try playing it.
Gosh, this is...
It's nice.
Of course it is. I've never used it.
There are more keys that I didn't press.
(Interested)
When did you get this?
I got it...
a year or two ago.
This one is nice.
Seeing its key condition, it's really new.
Right.
You're like a neighbor who adds comments while eating...
- next to a clothing shop. - That's right.
That's really important.
It's really new.
What's important is that I didn't lie about anything.
Of course not.
This must come with it, right?
Of course.
- I was really going to get one. - How much did you pay for it?
(Taking his phone out)
(AI84 looks for its price right away.)
The resale price...
is 600 to 700 dollars if it's in good condition.
We'll give it to you cheaper since it's you.
No, it's...
Six hundred dollars is a great price for me.
I'll take this at 600 dollars.
- It's sold! - I'll take this at 600 dollars.
- It's sold. - I didn't know that'd sell.
Yes!
- Since it's for a good cause, - That's right.
I'll gladly pay 600 dollars.
I'm personally really happy.
It couldn't even make a sound...
because it met a bad owner.
- I'm glad it found a good owner. - That's right.
I didn't think it'd sell.
I didn't have any expectation at all.
I'll write a new musical with this.
- Gosh. - With this keyboard.
With this keyboard.
(His eyes, nose, and mouth open at the news of a new musical.)
Was that a true reaction?
He must be happy.
I was moved because he said he'd use it.
Only Moorincess can react like that.
(Heart-stoppingly moving)
(The usage of the piano leveled up in an instant.)
(Oh, my goodness)
Come listen to the song when it's ready.
(The Tony Award winner will play my piano?)
Goodness. I hate that.
Oh, my.
First of all, I was really grateful.
On top of that, he said he'd write a new piece with it.
I was really moved.
I was so proud.
His gesture...
(Hyun Moo and the piano's 1st encounter in May, 2024)
(He dreamed of becoming Moozart after 6 years.)
- That was it. - Oh, no.
(And in 2026...)
It found a good owner.
It found a really good one.
(And what Hue said after seeing the keyboard)
(I'll write a new musical with this.)
I was really moved, that's why.
It looks like someone confessed to him.
- Like he was proposed. - Right?
How shall I put it? It felt like the piano...
became a human and smiled at me.
That's right.
(It felt like the piano smiled at me.)
Keyboard, you went through a lot.
You and I were so stressed, seeing each other.
Now, unfold your dream. It's your time.
You'll make a grander piece than "Maybe Happy Ending."
It found the right partner.
You got this.
I'll make sure to go and watch it.
- Don't lose that smile. - "Don't lose that smile."
"Adios, my piano."
I think I'm ready to pay.
- Okay. Let's go. - I'm done shopping.
It's time to settle the bill.
We'll settle the bill on the floor.
- How much was this? - This is 20 dollars.
Gosh, he got a lot.
Yes.
(He's still contemplating on the sweater.)
Gosh, this...
(Hyun Moo's fancy sweater he kept on hold)
Hue considers the usage of the items really importantly.
He's the complete opposite of me. I get it if it's from Gucci.
You'll have to party a lot because you became successful.
You'll party because the next piece will do well.
The next one will do well, so you'll party again.
If you keep wearing the same outfit at parties,
they'll go, "He's always wearing the same thing."
"I guess he's not so stylish."
But if you put that on, they'll go,
"Gosh, you can pull off a sweater like this, Hue?"
I'll buy it.
Yes!
(Cheering)
(After a long contemplation, he gets Hyun Moo's sweater.)
I'm sure there will be an occasion to wear it.
Since it's for a good cause...
It really looks good on him.
Of course. Who else could pull that off but him?
- That's right. - No one else can pull that off.
It's 600, 1,000, 1,250...
It's 1,270 dollars.
- Thank you. - Hue got a lot of stuff.
- It's 2,330 dollars. - It's 2,330 dollars?
Settling the bill must've been really tough.
Here's why it was hard to settle the bill.
There are no price tags on them.
- Right. - The prices kept changing.
- What? - Earlier, he said...
- it was 500 dollars. - Right.
When I'm about to settle, he goes, "I'll give it to you at 450."
- But I already wrote it's 500. - He has to erase it again.
Then I have to erase it and settle the bill again.
Right, you have to calculate again.
- That's a lot of work. - That's right.
I thought I withdrew...
quite a lot of cash.
- You can wire it to us too. - He got a lot.
For cash...
I have 2,000 dollars.
- Yes. You'll wire it. - I'll wire 330 dollars.
You have to make sure you wire it later.
I'll wire it to you right away.
It gets a little iffy if a day passes.
- It's hard to ask too. - I'll wire it right away.
- Then... - Here. I wired it.
Yes.
(Watching if he's wiring the money or not)
I think I've seen that face and comment a lot...
- when buying clothes... - That's right.
At an underground shopping mall.
They make such a face...
- if you don't pay with a card. - That's right.
- You have to withdraw money. - They love cash the most.
"We don't accept cards."
- It's all right. - Then...
- I should put them in a bag. - Go ahead.
I should put them in a bag.
Gosh, a luxury good.
Goodness.
Gucci, you met the wrong owner. Goodness.
Go to a nice place with a new owner.
"Go to a nice place?"
(Be happy there.)
I felt really bad.
I really think goods should find their owners.
- Of course. - They're always stuck...
in my dressing room.
(They're packing the goods while Hyun Moo says goodbye.)
CODE KUNST folds the clothes and puts them in well.
- You need to put them in well. - Of course.
He's good.
Here we go.
I received the money.
We'll help you carry the keyboard. Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Personally, I think he shopped the best.
He got the good ones and ones he'd wear.
Hyun Moo, you're going through a lot.
I should put it in right away.
You're the happiest when the biggest item gets sold.
- Thank you. - Sure.
- Bye. Thank you. - Bye.
Thank you for all the good items.
- I'll wear them well. - We'll hold it again.
All right.
(Gosh, it's tiring.)
Since we've sold quite a bit,
let's do an interim check.
Let's unpack them and hang them all.
- Which ones? These? - These. The new ones.
People can't think of unpacking and checking them.
People didn't check them out because they were packed.
Right. You should hang them all.
(They decided to unpack them to sell more.)
- Should I unpack it all? - Yes, we have to anyway.
It's better to unpack them.
Because they're packed, people don't check them.
Gosh, it's totally new.
(Under Seller CODE KUNST, they start organizing them.)
Let's unpack them all.
This one is pretty.
- What? - Please hang this too.
Someone is here.
I feel like it'd be Ju Seung.
- Ju Seung... - No, their hair is long.
(Rushing down at the ringing bell)
Who is it?
- Hi, Joy. Welcome. - Hello.
- It's me. - It's Joy.
I brought a lot of stuff.
Could you give me a hand?
- Okay. You have a lot of stuff too. - We can put it in here.
You're selling all these?
- Kian84! Give us a hand. - Okay.
Gosh, Joy, you brought so much. My goodness.
You brought three times more as soon as we sold some.
It felt daunting then.
(It's dizzying even when he sees it again.)
What is all this? Goodness.
How did you even pack all these?
- Gosh. - I mean...
You brought your clothes too?
(A bundle in each hand)
(The maximalist of items from social media)
(The online shopping master's items are here.)
She also has a lot of stuff.
I do.
Our items are in similar categories.
- That's right. It was completely... - When Joy came...
- The categories varied. - They were various.
Right. They're different.
Also, it was Joy's first flea market.
I selected them for a week.
Let's get rid of the useless things.
Let's move our stuff outside.
Gosh, what do we do with these?
It does feel daunting.
- Gosh. - That's a lot of stuff.
There was no space to display them.
Are you moving to another country?
Why did you... This must be...
Your house had all these?
- Yes. - Where must they've been?
They were all hidden.
Look at your face.
I'm a big shopper, but I thought you were one too.
These days, I have lost interest in material things.
- You have lost interest already? - Yes.
- "Already?" - Let's take them out first.
- Then... - Let's put them out.
You can use this counter to yourself.
Then I'll put them out.
- Really? - Who wears these glasses?
Hyun Moo brought them.
- I bought them from him. - He got them from me.
(Bursting into laughter)
- Oh, really? - Yes.
I didn't wear them once after buying them.
(He bought them at the Seorae Outlet 3 years ago.)
Seriously...
Things always come back around.
Like this?
You look good. Do you want to get them?
- They look good on you. - It's yours, Joy.
- I look good in them? - You... How much are they?
If you're buying them, I'll give them to you at ten dollars.
Like this?
- You film challenge videos a lot. - Yes.
- You should wear them in it. - He's right.
- I should get them. - Get them. It's ten dollars.
- It's sold. - It's sold.
Didn't you say you've lost interest in shopping?
She bought them 30 seconds...
after saying she's lost interest in shopping.
How can you get these at ten dollars?
- Right? - Yes.
- This is pretty too. - It's pretty.
- Oh, my. - Red pairing.
It's pretty.
It's perfect for your outfit.
- Really? - That's yours too, Hyun Moo.
- They're mine. - Right?
- I should get these too. - That's Hyun Moo's too.
This?
I thought you've lost interest in shopping.
I'm easily swayed.
You got two items in no time.
You're the fastest person to get something so far.
- Put them out for now. - Okay.
- They're keychains. - Keychains?
- Keychains. - Keychains.
You don't know what you'd get.
- Oh, it's a random box? - Yes.
- You'd want to get that. - Is it Labubu?
This is really cute.
If you hang this on your bag...
Oh, this is...
- It's popular these days. - It's not fake, is it?
- No, it's not. - Okay.
I bought this in Sapporo.
Is it "Frozen" merch?
- Yes. - It's a princess set.
- Yes, a princess set. - We could have a father over.
They'd like it.
Oh, that's an essence for hair loss.
Hyun Moo.
- Hyun Moo, it's for hair loss. - How much is it?
Two dollars per essence.
- Two dollars? - Yes. Two dollars per essence.
(I can't hold myself back from buying it.)
I sprayed it three times already.
- It's good, right? - How is it?
I can't tell yet.
Right? Then it'd win a Nobel Prize.
It's a foot massager.
- How much is this? - Three dollars.
Three dollars.
Joy, you sell things well.
- I... - She sells things well.
- She's good. - Yes. She's good.
It keeps your butt warm.
Why would you get that, Hyun Moo?
Warm butt keeps you healthy.
- How much is it? - Ten dollars.
- For real? - It's ten dollars.
I think your spending habit...
- is similar to mine. - Right.
- He doesn't doubt at all. - I don't doubt.
Wait, that's...
(The donation king spotted something again.)
(Impressed)
This... Try it on.
You're selling this to me?
It's pretty. Look.
It was a bit big for me.
Men wear Vivienne Westwood backpacks a lot these days.
They're all genderless.
Should I get it?
- Which one? - What kind of expression is that?
Do you want me to be honest?
I avoid people like you if I meet them on the streets.
- For real. - Why? It's pretty.
This is a really cute hat.
What do you think of this?
I feel like...
I've seen this scene a lot in Dongdaemun.
Let me see. It's so cute!
- It's yours. - It's so cute.
My head's gone numb.
(Shy)
- It's really cute. - I feel like he'd be friends...
with the guy with that backpack.
- But I really meant it. - My head's numb.
- It's cute. - Right?
It's cute.
Why do you have so much stuff?
- She brought so much stuff. - Are we done?
- We have five more. - What?
Can this fit a person?
Whose cloth is that?
I really thought some were for dogs.
- How can you fit in this? - It's a pretty one.
- It's a crop top. - It is pretty, but...
It's for dogs.
(Surprised)
(Joy's room is almost ready.)
(Miscellaneous goods section)
(Clothes section)
- Look how various her items are. - I know.
(Shoes section)
I hated that sound.
(A customer came at a great time.)
Oh, hello, Tae Hyun.
- Hyun Moo. - Oh, Tae Hyun.
(Actor Cha Tae Hyun)
(A master actor of everyday performances...)
(that mirror daily life's warmth)
(Nation's beloved actor, Cha Tae Hyun)
(Moomoo's close friend who gladly came to donate)
- Hyun Moo. - Oh, Tae Hyun.
He's a year older than me.
- Really? - Yes.
When will you stop being surprised?
Thank you for coming, Hyun Moo.
Please write a comment on the guestbook.
- Gosh. - He still has a boyish charm.
- That's right. - Yes.
He has a boyish charm.
What are you buying here?
I have no idea.
It's what I drew. "Moomoo Market."
One of the keyboards is sold.
My keyboard is sold.
- Who bought the keyboard? - Writer Hue Park.
"Maybe Happy Ending."
(Not interested, keeping his hands in his pocket)
It looks like you're not interested in buying things.
I know. He's a really difficult type to sell things.
That's right.
There's nothing I can buy.
- What is this? - An equestrian machine.
Who'd buy this?
It was already sold.
It was already sold, which is even more surprising.
There's no space for this. Whose thing is this?
- Mine. - Why did you get this?
(It is fun, actually.)
- Do you want to move faster? - Yes, make it faster.
- Don't regret it. - Regret...
Yes.
- Hello. - Hi. Gosh, this is...
(Hello)
(Hi. Gosh, this is...)
We're saying hello at an awkward timing.
It's nice to meet you.
- What is this? - Oh, dear.
Goodness, this is unsightly.
- It's nice to meet you. - You are...
- You're riding a horse. - good at horse riding.
If I take this home, my wife would scold me.
Come on.
Is this all, by the way?
- There's more upstairs. - Okay. Let's go upstairs.
What's this? Should I put it away?
There's still more of Joy's stuff.
Tae Hyun, there's nothing that interests you here, right?
Items upstairs are crazy good.
Hello. It's been so long.
Wait. What is this?
Joy.
(Looking around the concept store on the 2nd floor)
Many of CODE KUNST's clothes are here.
That means they're stylish.
But many of my clothes were sold.
- Dex swept them all. - Someone bought them?
- Dex and... - Dex did?
(Anxious)
Honestly, I don't really know.
The fact that he put his hands in his pockets...
- means he's really picky. - That's right.
"I'm not going to buy any."
Which area interests you the most?
- I'm not interested in any. - Really?
(Strictly defending)
They're demotivated.
There's nothing I want to buy.
I see.
The kings of sales aren't saying anything.
- Then, how old is your daughter? - Exactly.
- My daughter is in eighth grade. - Oh, dear.
- She's going to be in ninth grade. - Eight or ninth grade?
- Let's go to Joy's room. - Yes.
Gosh, there's more?
- Joy's room. - There are cosmetics too.
There are many things you can buy for your daughter.
There are many shoes here.
- How big are her feet? - Her shoe size.
The 1 in 8th grade...
(The strict customer finally took out his hands.)
- He opened his heart. - He took out his hands.
- He's a father. - He is, indeed.
That was a good strategy.
- It's 235mm. - It's what Joy used to wear.
It's Birkenstock. You must get it.
(All eyes on him)
- Yes. - They'd fit.
- Finally. - He's won over.
My daughter who's in eighth grade has small feet.
(She has small feet.)
- You're right. - There are many cute hats too.
Nice. She doesn't wear hats much anyway.
It's demotivating.
(What do we do?)
This one is in trend these days.
Oh, it's Labubu.
(If that's the case...)
- A keychain? She likes keychains. - Yes.
- Yes, that's good. - A keychain sounds good.
- My second kid... - Finally!
Hangs around 25 keychains on her bag.
Then you must get the keychain.
- She loves keyrings. - They must be really close.
He's a fool for his daughter.
I should call her and show her this.
- Tae Eun. - What is it, Dad?
You know, it's a keychain.
- It's cute! - She likes it.
- This... - Yes.
Joy is selling it.
Do you want this?
- Yes, get a lot, Dad. - This...
Right? Isn't it really cute?
Hello.
(Without missing the chance, she starts selling it herself.)
It's not fake. Don't you like Kurumi?
- Dad, get them. - Okay.
"Dad, get them."
Your daughter said get them all.
Aren't they so cute? How cute!
- The keychains are really nice. - Good.
(How about this, sweetie?)
(She likes it too.)
(She likes this too.)
(I'll take that too.)
(Tae Hyun, the fool for his girl, goes wild with his shopping.)
(You can try it on.)
It's all genderless.
(Right then, someone arrived.)
Sung Tae.
(Other people came after hearing about the market.)
(The grateful people...)
(who will join the generous donation have entered.)
(The doorbell rings like crazy.)
(This is the grand flea market.)
(Welcome)
(Do you like camping?)
(The killer-item, a tent, appears.)
Like this.
(Your toes are twisted, right?)
(How did you know?)
(Buy this and fix them.)
(An all-items flea market has grand prizes too.)
A princess.
(I'll buy it.)
(The result of wild marketing...)
(is donation beyond imagination?)
(Even the donation fairy approves of it.)
(The total is...)
(Everyone is surprised by the total donation.)
I'll return as much as I received.
(Donate Grandly)
(Amazed)
(I can tell that it's 2,500cc from the sound.)
(Where is this place filled with motorcycles?)
(A strong engine sound)
(Sung Hwan is at a motorbike shop.)
(A helmet is a must.)
(A long-time dream of mine)
(A motorbike)
(This sound isn't made from my mouth.)
(I'll show you how riders ride it.)
(I'm so cool.)
(I don't have the class 2 small vehicle license.)
(Embarrassed)
(I failed twice for the class 2 small vehicle license.)
(It's the day of my third try.)
(Going out of line)
(Going out of line again)
(This isn't easy.)
(This is easy.)
(His close friend Lee Jong Hyuk...)
(who has experience teaching his kids)
(I'll show you as the senior class 2 small vehicle license holder.)
(How do you start this thing?)
(Do I have to press something?)
(Jun Su's dad, where are you going?)
(What's with this guy?)
(There's no time for this!)
- That's it! - All right.
(With Jong Hyuk's help, )
(he practices like crazy.)
(Start)
(With confidence, )
(he's arrived at the testing center.)
I'm finally here.
(Nervous)
(The long-awaited moment...)
(is finally here.)
Your test will begin.
(Focused)
(Don't be nervous.)
It's today or never.
(Go, Ku Motorcycle)